Where's the bird?
鸟在哪里
It's in the cage.
在笼子里
Is it red and blue?
是红色和蓝色的吗
No, it isn't.
不 不是
It's red and green.
它是红色和绿色的
Where are the dogs?
狗在哪里
They are behind the flowers.
它们在花的后面
Are they gray and brown?
它们是灰色和棕色的吗
No, they aren't.
不 它们不是
They're black and white.
它们是黑白的
Where are the rabbits?
兔子在哪里
They are under the table.
它们在桌子下面
Are they black and white?
它们是黑白的吗
No, they aren't.
不 它们不是
They're brown and white.
它们是棕色和白色的
Where are the fish?
鱼在哪里
They are in the tank.
它们在水箱里
Are they orange?
它们是橙色的吗
No, they aren't.
不 它们不是
They are red and yellow.
它们是红色和黄色的
Where are the cats?
猫在哪里
They're on the wall.
它们在墙上
Are they green and yellow?
它们是绿色和黄色的吗
No, they aren't.
不是
They're black and gray.
它们是黑色和灰色的